Think twice before plugging your phone into any public USB charging station.
It seems super convenient when your battery is low, but these stations are a major security risk.
Criminals can easily modify them. They can install malicious software.
This trick is called juice jacking. When you connect your phone,
that hidden malware can instantly infect your device.
It can steal all your personal data.
We're talking passwords, photos, banking details, even your identity.
Your phone isn't just getting power, it's making a data connection to an unknown computer.
And that computer might be controlled by hackers.
It's a huge privacy nightmare waiting to happen.
To stay safe, always use your own wall charger plugged into an AC outlet or carry a power bank.